let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The full form of CSS is:",
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheet",
    options: [
        "Common Style Sheet",
        "Colorful Style Sheet",
        "Computer Style Sheet",
        "Cascading Style Sheet"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following tag is used to embed css in html page?",
    answer: "style",
    options: [
      "css",
      "style",
      "!DOCTYPE html",
      "script"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following CSS selectors are used to specify a group of elements?",
    answer: "class",
    options: [
      "tag",
      "class",
      "id",
      "both class and tag"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following has introduced text, list, box, margin, border, color, and background properties?",
    answer: "CSS",
    options: [
      "HTML",
      "PHP",
      "Ajax",
      "CSS"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does XML stand for?",
    answer: "eXtensible Markup Language",
    options: [
      "eXtensible Markup Language",
      "eXecutable Multiple Language",
      "eXTra Multi-Program Language",
      "eXamine Multiple Language"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How can you created rounded corners using CSS3?",
    answer: "border[round]: 30px",
    options: [
      "border[round]: 30px",
      "corner-effect: round",
      "border-radius: 30px",
      "alpha-effect: round-corner"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following CSS framework is used to create a responsive design?",
    answer: "bootstrap",
    options: [
      "django",
      "larawell",
      "rails",
      "bootstrap"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following CSS property is used to make the text bold?",
    answer: "font-weight: bold",
    options: [
      "font-weight: bold",
      "font-style: bold",
      "text-align: bold",
      "text-decoration: bold"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following CSS style property is used to specify an italic text?",
    answer: "font-style",
    options: [
      "style",
      "font-style",
      "font",
      "All of These"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following are the CSS Extension Prefixes for Webkit?",
    answer: "-webkit",
    options: [
      "-webkit",
      "-o-",
      " -web",
      " -chrome"
    ]
  },
];